Kitchen & Dining[Kitchen](https://www.houzz.com/photos/kitchen-ideas-and-designs-phbr0-bp~t_709)[Dining Room](https://www.houzz.com/photos/dining-room-ideas-phbr0-bp~t_722)[Pantry](https://www.houzz.com/photos/kitchen-pantry-ideas-phbr1-bp~t_709~a_13-517)[Great Room](https://www.houzz.com/photos/great-room-ideas-phbr1-bp~t_722~a_13-3)[Breakfast Nook](https://www.houzz.com/photos/breakfast-nook-ideas-phbr0lbl-bl~l_18)

Living[Living Room](https://www.houzz.com/photos/living-room-ideas-phbr0-bp~t_718)[Family Room](https://www.houzz.com/photos/family-room-ideas-phbr0-bp~t_720)[Sunroom](https://www.houzz.com/photos/sunroom-ideas-phbr0-bp~t_12300)

Bed & Bath[Bathroom](https://www.houzz.com/photos/bathroom-ideas-phbr0-bp~t_712)[Powder Room](https://www.houzz.com/photos/powder-room-ideas-phbr0-bp~t_713)[Bedroom](https://www.houzz.com/photos/bedroom-ideas-and-designs-phbr0-bp~t_715)[Storage & Closet](https://www.houzz.com/photos/closet-ideas-phbr0-bp~t_734)[Baby & Kids](https://www.houzz.com/photos/baby-and-kids-design-ideas-phbr0-bp~t_730)

Utility[Laundry](https://www.houzz.com/photos/laundry-room-ideas-and-designs-phbr0-bp~t_753)[Garage](https://www.houzz.com/photos/garage-ideas-and-designs-phbr0-bp~t_24680)[Mudroom](https://www.houzz.com/photos/mudroom-ideas-and-designs-phbr1-bp~t_741~a_13-415)

Outdoor[Landscape](https://www.houzz.com/photos/landscaping-ideas-phbr0-bp~t_728)[Patio](https://www.houzz.com/photos/patio-ideas-and-designs-phbr0-bp~t_725)[Deck](https://www.houzz.com/photos/deck-ideas-phbr0-bp~t_912)[Pool](https://www.houzz.com/photos/pool-ideas-phbr0-bp~t_727)[Backyard](https://www.houzz.com/photos/backyard-landscaping-ideas-and-designs-phbr1-bp~t_728~a_38-251)[Porch](https://www.houzz.com/photos/porch-ideas-phbr0-bp~t_726)[Exterior](https://www.houzz.com/photos/exterior-home-ideas-phbr0-bp~t_736)[Outdoor Kitchen](https://www.houzz.com/photos/outdoor-kitchen-design-ideas-phbr1-bp~t_724~a_34-239)[Front Yard](https://www.houzz.com/photos/front-yard-landscaping-ideas-and-designs-phbr1-bp~t_728~a_38-250)[Driveway](https://www.houzz.com/photos/driveway-ideas-and-designs-phbr1-bp~t_728~a_13-13787)[Poolhouse](https://www.houzz.com/photos/pool-house-ideas-phbr1-bp~t_727~a_34-539)

Bar & Wine[Home Bar](https://www.houzz.com/photos/home-bar-ideas-phbr0-bp~t_12302)[Wine Cellar](https://www.houzz.com/photos/wine-cellar-ideas-and-designs-phbr0-bp~t_755)

More Rooms[Game Room](https://www.houzz.com/photos/game-room-ideas-phbr1-bp~t_720~a_34-480)[Home Office](https://www.houzz.com/photos/home-office-ideas-phbr0-bp~t_732)[Basement](https://www.houzz.com/photos/basement-ideas-phbr0-bp~t_747)[Craft](https://www.houzz.com/photos/craft-room-ideas-and-designs-phbr1-bp~t_732~a_34-397)[Library](https://www.houzz.com/photos/family-room-library-ideas-phbr1-bp~t_720~a_34-482)[Gym](https://www.houzz.com/photos/home-gym-ideas-phbr0-bp~t_751)

Popular Design Ideas[Kitchen Backsplash](https://www.houzz.com/photos/kitchen-backsplash-ideas-phbr1-bp~t_709~a_21-999999)[Firepit](https://www.houzz.com/photos/fire-pit-ideas-phbr1-bp~t_724~a_34-282)[Fireplace](https://www.houzz.com/photos/fireplace-designs-and-ideas-phbr1-bp~t_718~a_48-999999)[Deck Railing](https://www.houzz.com/photos/deck-ideas-phbr1-bp~t_912~a_1412-999999)[Pergola](https://www.houzz.com/photos/pergola-ideas-phbr1-bp~t_724~a_41-296)[Privacy Fence](https://www.houzz.com/photos/privacy-landscaping-ideas-phbr1-bp~t_728~a_34-20599)[Small Closet](https://www.houzz.com/photos/small-closet-ideas-phbr1-bp~t_734~a_30-231)

Stories and Guides[Popular Stories](https://www.houzz.com/ideabooks/most-popular-stories-on-houzz)[Renovation Cost Guides](https://www.houzz.com/cost-guides)[Fence Installation Cost Guide](https://www.houzz.com/cost/10-cost-to-install-a-fence)[Window Installation Cost Guide](https://www.houzz.com/cost/11-cost-to-install-or-replace-a-window)

Get Advice[Design Dilemmas](https://www.houzz.com/discussions/design-dilemma)[Before & After](https://www.houzz.com/discussions/before-and-after)

* Popular Professionals
* Design & Planning
* Construction & Renovation
* Finishes & Fixtures
* Landscaping & Outdoor
* Systems & Appliances
* More
* 

* Popular
* Furniture
* Bath
* Outdoor
* Rugs & Decor
* Lighting
* Home Improvement
* Kitchen & Tabletop
* More

* Designer Picks

Looking for the perfect gift? Send a [Houzz Gift Card!](https://www.houzz.com/gift-card)

Cancel

[

UP TO 65% OFF

The Ultimate Vanity Sale](https://www.houzz.com/ideabooks/108801176) 

[

UP TO 75% OFF

The Ultimate Bedroom Sale](https://www.houzz.com/ideabooks/120778100) 

[

UP TO 75% OFF

Bestselling Bedroom Storage](https://www.houzz.com/ideabooks/171361306) 

[

UP TO 70% OFF

Bathroom Renovation Must-Haves](https://www.houzz.com/ideabooks/172837276) 

Your shopping cart is empty.

Houzz Pro: One simple solution for contractors and design pros

BACK

    * Kitchen & Dining
    * Living
    
    * Bed & Bath
    * Utility
    
    * Outdoor
    
    * Bar & Wine
    * More Rooms
    
    * Popular Design Ideas
    
    * Stories and Guides
    
    * Get Advice

    * Popular Professionals

    * Design & Planning

    * Construction & Renovation

    * Finishes & Fixtures

    * Landscaping & Outdoor

    * Systems & Appliances

    * More

    * Popular

        * 

    * Furniture

    * Bath

    * Outdoor

    * Rugs & Decor

    * Lighting

    * Home Improvement

    * Kitchen & Tabletop

    * More

    * Stories & Guides

    * Get Advice

    * View More

    * View More

    * View More

    * View More

    * View More

    * View More

    * View More

ABOUT

PRIVACY & LEGAL

* [Privacy](https://www.houzz.com/privacyPolicy) & [Notice](https://www.houzz.com/privacyPolicy#12)

SETTINGS

**PRIVACY POLICY**
==================

_Houzz is the leading platform for home remodeling and design, providing an all-in-one software solution for industry professionals and tools for homeowners to update their homes from start to finish. Using Houzz, people can find ideas and inspiration, hire professionals, and shop for products. Houzz Pro provides home industry professionals with a business management and marketing SaaS solution that helps them to win projects, collaborate with clients and teams, and run their business efficiently and profitably._

This Privacy Policy describes what personal information we collect through the Platform (defined below), how we use this information, how this information may be shared, and what choices and rights you have with respect to this information. Access and use of our Platform is subject to this Privacy Policy. The collection of personal data of job applicants is governed by the [Job Applicant Privacy Notice](https://help.houzz.com/s/article/Houzz-Privacy-Notice-Job-Applicants?language=en_US).

Our "Platform" is made up of [www.houzz.com](http://www.houzz.com/), [pro.houzz.com](http://pro.houzz.com/), [www.ivy.co](http://www.ivy.co/), and all of the related websites (including Houzz Pro), mobile apps, products, software, services, programs, and networks offered by Houzz, including our plug-ins and browser extensions.

The terms "we," "us," "our," or "Houzz" refer to the "[Houzz Group](https://help.houzz.com/s/article/Houzz-group?language=en_US)," including Houzz Inc., Houzz Shop LLC, and their corporate affiliates. By "you," we are referring to visitors and users of any part of our Platform.

The term "merchant" includes sellers and vendors of products available on the e-commerce marketplace on the Platform.

**1\. Collection of Information**
---------------------------------

We collect personal information that you provide us, from third parties, and automatically when you use our Platform. We collect information associated with your device using cookies and similar technologies. We may also receive information about your location.

### **Information You Provide Us**

We collect information that you provide us, including your account and profile information, content you submit or post to our Platform, your purchase information, your communications, and information you provide to us as part of surveys and contests.

**Account and Profile Information.** When you create an account on our Platform, we collect information you provide us, like your name, email address, interests, gender, age, and profile information. If you are a professional, you may also provide us information related to your business, including a business name, description, phone number, and areas served. If you use financial tools or services offered through our Platform, for example, to request or accept payments for your business services, we collect information to facilitate those transactions, such as copies of identification cards, proof of business ownership, bank name, account numbers, tax numbers and other business documentation as needed to verify your identity or integrate with our service providers.

**Content You Submit.** We collect information and content that you submit, share, or create across our Platform and on other websites that link to this Privacy Policy. This includes information and content submitted, shared, or created, including but not limited to your company information, profile picture, reviews, messages, comments, searches, photos, style preferences, ideabooks, discussion, project details, project costs, project timelines, change orders, and invoices.

**Purchases.** If you purchase or sell products or services or make or receive payments within our Platform, we collect certain information in order to complete your purchases, sales, and payments, such as your phone number, address, and payment method (for example, credit card or bank account information). If you participate in our Trade Program or Business Program, you may be asked to provide proof that you are eligible for the program or for a tax exemption.

**Communications.** When you communicate with us (via email, phone, through our Platform, through our chatbots, or otherwise) and when you use our Platform to communicate with others, we may record, monitor, collect, and use details about you and your communications (including call time and call duration). Certain professionals on our Platform may choose to use our call tracking feature in order to better manage their business. You are using our Platform when you make calls to these professionals using their phone number displayed on our Platform. We will provide you notice or obtain your consent in accordance with applicable law before recording or monitoring any of these calls. Otherwise, to the extent you communicate with professionals, sellers, and other users outside our Platform, those communications are not subject to this Privacy Policy.

**Surveys and Contests.** If you participate in our surveys, contests, or promotions, we will collect the information you provide to us.

### **Information from Others**

We collect information that others make available to us, including information from other platforms, publicly available information, information from other users of our Platform, information from our partners, service providers, and corporate affiliates, and information from third-party sites.

**Other Platforms.** We may receive information about you from third-party platforms when you allow the third-party platform to share this information with us or allow Houzz to obtain this information from the third party. For example, we may receive information such as your name, email address, and profile photo when you sign-up for our Platform through Facebook, Google, or Apple. We may also receive information about you when you upload your contacts from your third-party email service; use our Platform (or a third-party integration on our Platform) to manage your calendar on another platform or to manage and send communications (e.g., email or text messages).

**Publicly Available Information.** If you are a professional, or merchant we may collect and verify information about you from publicly available sources and where permitted by applicable law or, with your permission, make it available as part of our Platform. For example, we may receive your name and contact information from industry associations and dealer networks in which you participate and display your affiliation with these organizations. We also may collect and display the details of any license you have using publicly available records.

**Other Users and Customers.** Others may post content on our Platform that includes information about you (for example, as part of photos, stories, and reviews) or provide us your information in connection with using our Platform (e.g., to manage their business, organize photoshoots of their projects, participate in referral programs, and to advertise through our Platform). In order to enhance the quality of our Platform, professionals and sellers on our Platform may provide us information about your engagement with them, including whether you have contacted them or responded to them, whether your project has been completed, and whether you have received a product you have ordered. If you are a professional or merchant, Platform users and visitors may provide us with feedback and public reviews about you.

**Our Partners and Service Providers.** We may receive information about you from our partners and service providers. For example, our payment processors may update your payment information, advertising partners may help us send communications to your address, and third parties may help us prevent fraud by verifying your contact information. In addition, our financial partners that conduct "know your customer" or "know your business" (KYC or KYB) verification and our banking partners that issue the Houzz credit card(s) may provide us with information they collect directly from you. For example, they may share with us information used to verify your identity, whether you have a Houzz credit card, related to any card reward or loyalty program, or resulting from prescreening you for card offers.

**Houzz Group.** In accordance with applicable laws and subject to this and additional privacy policies, Houzz Group entities may receive information about you from other Houzz Group entities.

**Third-Party Sites.** Certain third-party sites embed a Houzz plug-in, widget, or content, including through Houzz-branded buttons, badges, and slideshows and Houzz co-branded content partnerships. Our plug-ins, widgets, embedded content, and pixels may collect information pursuant to our [Cookie Policy](https://www.houzz.com/cookiePolicy). You may also choose to use our browser extensions, which collect the information described in this Privacy Policy like the rest of our Platform.

**Website Services.** Website Services means any website displaying pro content and other content included by or on behalf of you into standard Houzz web templates with hosting managed by Houzz. As with the rest of our Platform, we collect the information described in this Privacy Policy when providing Website Services, including your messages to professionals sent through those sites. Professionals collect usage information for their websites and receive your messages sent through those sites.

### **Automatically Collected Information**

Each time you access the Platform, information is sent to our server by your Internet browser or app and stored in our log files. We collect information about your use of our Platform, including your search activity, the pages you view, the date and time of your visit, and if you use our browser extensions, the content you interact with on third-party sites (for example, if you save an image from a third-party site to your Houzz account), and how you navigate and interact with a page or screen. We also collect information that your device provides to us in connection with your use of our Platform, such as your browser type, type of device, browser language, IP address, mobile carrier, unique device identifier, and requested and referring URLs.

### **Cookies and Similar Technologies**

We use cookies and similar technologies in connection with your use of our Platform to collect information related to what you see and interact with on our Platform and other Platform access and use. Please see our [Cookie Policy](https://www.houzz.com/cookiePolicy) for more information on our use of cookies and how to accept or opt-out of cookies, but please note that unless required by law, we do not change system behavior within our Platform in response to browser requests not to be tracked.

### **Location Information**

We may receive your device's location if you enable this through your browser or mobile device. We may infer your general location from your IP address. You may also choose to provide us your location information by inputting this information in our Platform, including in your Houzz settings, Ivy settings, or when you checkout as a shipping or billing address.

**2\. Use of Information**
--------------------------

We use the personal information we collect to provide, support, and personalize our Platform and to communicate with you about our Platform (on and off our Platform). The ways we do this include the following:

* to provide and improve our Platform and its features and functionality, including to display content you post publicly, fulfill your purchases through our Platform, process, store, and deliver your communications; to provide customer service and support; to respond to your inquiries or requests; to back-up our systems; and to improve the security of our Platform;
* to evaluate use of our Platform for our business purposes and to provide and improve our products and services, including new and co-branded products and services and our Platform's functionality;
* to personalize your experience, such as tailoring the content and information made available to you and our support services;
* to display relevant or targeted advertising (on our Platform and third-party sites) for us and other businesses and to evaluate the success of such advertising;
* to provide feedback to professionals and merchants on our Platform;
* to communicate with you as described in our agreements with you (for example, the Houzz [Terms of Use](https://www.houzz.com/termsOfUse)) or this Privacy Policy;
* to prevent fraud and to maintain a quality experience for our business purposes or legal reasons, including to filter for spam and communications that violate our agreements with you (for example, the Houzz [Terms of Use](https://www.houzz.com/termsOfUse));
* to enforce compliance with our agreements with you (for example, the Houzz [Terms of Use](https://www.houzz.com/termsOfUse)) and applicable law; to comply with our legal obligations; to prosecute or defend a lawsuit, arbitration, or similar legal proceeding; to respond to lawful requests by public authorities (including national security or law enforcement requirements);
* to perform research and analysis for our business purposes and to conduct journalist research; and
* to award badges and similar designations and if you decide to participate, to administer surveys, contests, and promotions.

Additional Information About Our Uses of Information

**Contacts**. If you provide us information about your contacts (for example, when you sign up for our Platform through Facebook), in order to facilitate a more connected experience, we may inform your contacts who have accounts on our Platform that you also have joined our Platform and follow them on your behalf so that you may view their public activities on our Platform.

**Communications**. We may use your communications generally for quality assurance purposes and training, and to improve our products and services. We may use your communications to understand and help manage the quality of requests received, and responses sent, by professionals and sellers on our Platform and to provide them with feedback. We may use automated technology to review your communications and improve user experience. [Learn more](https://help.houzz.com/s/article/Automated-Communications-Technology?language=en_US).

**Device and Activity Data**. We use your device information, IP address and other information we collect from cookies and similar technologies for personalization, advertising and operating our websites. Some of the information we collect from using cookies is essential to provide the Platform's services to you, such as helping you log in your account; other uses of this information assists us with the performance and functionality of the Platform, such as remembering your site preferences or items you have placed in your shopping cart; and other uses of this information enables us to analyze site usage and improve the Platform.

We also enable our service providers, third-party businesses advertising on our Platform, advertising networks, and advertising partners to use cookies or similar technologies to track your activities on our Platform and other online properties in order to provide you with tailored ads across websites, apps, and devices and to understand how those ads perform. To learn how to opt-out of cookie tracking please see our [Cookie Policy](https://www.houzz.com/cookiePolicy).

**Purchases and Payment Information**. For your convenience, we and our payment processors will store information about the payment method you use in connection with the Platform. Note that while our payment processors may store your complete credit card number, Houzz does not. You may remove or change your payment method on Houzz through your [settings](https://www.houzz.com/settingsAdvanced). If you would like to change your payment method on Ivy and you use a credit card, please go to your [Ivy settings](https://members.ivy.co/users/sign_in). If you make purchases on Houzz as a visitor and subsequently create an account, for your reference, we will make information available to you about any prior purchases completed using the email address for your account. If you are a client on Ivy, we use your information to show you all of your payments, as well as invoices, proposals, retainers, and similar documents on a per-project basis.

**Location**. With your permission, we use your location information to provide you with location-based alerts for your projects, for example, we may tell you the weather conditions or remind you to start or stop your project timers. You can stop sharing your location for these purposes at any time, by updating your device settings.

**3\. Sharing Your Information**
--------------------------------

We share your personal information in the following ways:

### **Platform Visitors and Users**

One of the main purposes of having a Houzz account is to share home renovation and design ideas with others. Through Houzz, others have the ability to find, contact, view, and follow your profile and public activity on Houzz (for example, if you "like'' content on our Platform or if you create an ideabook and do not mark it private) and link it to your username. You can customize your Houzz profile and whether users may follow you through your Houzz [settings](https://www.houzz.com/settingsAdvanced). Your Houzz content (for example, ideabooks, photos, notes on others' photos, projects, discussions, and social media profiles), followers, and others you follow are publicly viewable on the Platform and open to comments by other Houzz users. If you would like to make certain of your content private, please click [here](https://help.houzz.com/s/article/How-do-I-adjust-my-privacy-settings?language=en_US) for more information. If you are a professional, or merchant on Houzz, we may also display the following information in order to help visitors and users evaluate you: aggregated information on our Platform about your Platform activity (e.g. response rate), and information that is publicly available from third parties.

### **Professionals, Merchants, and Other Businesses on our Platform**

If you request us to find professionals for you, your project information (including the contact information) that you provide will be made available to a limited number of professionals that we believe may be suitable for your project. Such professionals are independent from Houzz and their use of your data is not covered by this Privacy Policy. Professionals and merchants that participate on the Houzz Platform may view your public activities on our Platform and receive feedback you provide to us about your engagement with them. For example, if you requested us to find professionals for you and provide us feedback about your level of interest in these professionals, we may convey such feedback to them. In addition, a professional or merchant can view your public activities on our Platform that are interactions with their content (for example, that you added one of their photos to your non-private ideabook on a particular date, as identified by the username for your profile and any photo or public identifiers you provide for your profile). When you receive messages from professionals through the Platform, Houzz and the professionals can track your interaction with these messages and phone calls, including whether you opened the messages or answered the phone call, or documents shared with these messages. A professional or merchant cannot see your non-public account information or see private activity (for example, if your ideabook is private).

### **Service Providers and Partners**

We may share your information with service providers to help us operate our Platform and provide services to you. For example, we ask third parties to help us perform the following types of services: payment processing; telecommunications; product sales and support; logistics, delivery, and order fulfillment; marketing and advertising; IT services; fraud detection; customer management; and analytics providers to help us understand user behavior on our Platform. We also use service providers and partners to perform services explained in our [Cookie Policy](https://www.houzz.com/cookiePolicy). You can find more information [here](https://help.houzz.com/s/article/Service-Providers-and-Platform-Partners?language=en_US) about our service providers and partners with which we may share your information. Only if you specifically agree to share your contact information with a third-party partner, for example, as part of a contest or promotion we sponsor with such a third party, will we share your contact information with that third-party partner for their direct marketing purposes.

In addition, we may share information about you with third-party platforms when you allow the third-party platform to receive this information from us or allow Houzz to share this information with the third party. Our Platform may include third-party social media features and other third-party plug-ins and widgets. When these features are displayed on our Platform, they are operated or hosted by third parties. We are not responsible for these third parties and third-party platforms, so please carefully review their privacy policies and your permissions granted to these third parties and platforms. For example, you may sign-up for our Platform through Google or Apple.

### **Advertisers and Ad Networks**

We use advertising networks and partners to serve advertisements for us and other businesses, including interest-based advertising, on third-party sites and to assist us in evaluating the effectiveness of our advertising. We may also work with advertising networks and partners to serve ads on our Platform and to communicate with you at the addresses they have for you. We may provide advertising networks, advertising partners, and businesses advertising on our Platform with aggregate information but other than hashed information or device identifiers, we do not disclose your name, contact information, or other personal information. For example, we may provide a hashed version of your email address or other information to advertising networks (e.g., Facebook and Google) to serve advertisements to you or others. Depending on where you live, you may have the right to opt out of the sharing of your information for this purpose, to learn how to opt out please see the Your Choices and Rights section of this Privacy Policy.

### **Corporate Affiliates and Business Transfers**

We may share information from or about you with: (a) other companies in the Houzz Group, or (b) a potential or actual acquirer, successor, or assignee as part of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets, or stock (including bankruptcy or similar proceedings) to another company. We may share your personal information with that company and its advisors before and after the transaction date. In the event of a sale or transfer of our business results, we will notify you in the same way we notify you of a material change to this Privacy Policy.

### **Legal Obligations**

We may disclose information from or about you, as required or permitted by applicable law, if we believe that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with legal process and law enforcement instructions and orders, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on us, a service provider, or a partner (which may include disclosure to law enforcement, courts, or governmental authorities); (b) prevent, investigate, or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with our Platform; (c) protect our rights, reputation, property, or that of our visitors, users, corporate affiliates, or the public; or (d) enforce compliance with our agreements with you (for example, the Houzz [Terms of Use](https://www.houzz.com/termsOfUse)).

**4\. Communications**
----------------------

An essential part of our services that you sign up for when you create an account on our Platform is to receive communications from us or our professional partners through email, phone call, and text message, or through our Platform. If you use our mobile app, these communications also include push notifications. We communicate with you about your account, privacy, use of the Platform, including interactions with your content (for example, if others "like" your ideabook, respond to your comment, or if you earn a badge on our Platform), news relating to the Platform, its features and industry developments, and communications concerning promotions run by us or third parties. We also ask for your feedback about your experience in connection with our Platform or about your home renovation and design plans. In accordance with applicable law, we or our professional partners may send you marketing communications (e.g., with tips, offers, and similar services). These communications may feature us, our Platform, co-branded products and services, professionals, merchants, and other businesses on our Platform.

If you provide us your phone number, we and our professional partners may call you or send you text messages to help you with using the Platform (e.g., to discuss your home remodeling or design project, to find professionals, to assist with your order, or if you are a professional, to find products or to provide you tips about your professional profile). If you are a professional or other business, we may use your contact information (whether publicly available or provided to Houzz) to call and otherwise contact you about our Platform, including to market and sell our products or services or those available on our Platform.

Our Platform also allows you and others to send messages and make calls in our Platform, share content with others outside our Platform, and if you make your contact information available, for others to contact you outside of our Platform.

**5\. Your Choices and Rights**
-------------------------------

Depending on where you live and how you use our Platform, you may have certain rights relating to your personal information. Below we explain how to exercise these rights:

**Access to Information**. You can ask us to confirm if we are processing your personal information, provide you with details about our processing, and access much of the information you have provided us by logging into your account. To request access to both your Houzz or Ivy information contact us as provided in the Contact Us section.

**Correct Your Information**. You can update your information within your profile settings and modify content that contains information about you from your account. To edit your personal information, visit your profile in your Houzz [settings](https://www.houzz.com/settingsAdvanced) and Ivy [settings](https://members.ivy.co/designers/account_info). You may also contact us about correcting or updating your personal information using the methods provided in the Contact Us section.

**Download Your Information.** You may request to receive a copy of your Houzz information through your Houzz [settings](https://www.houzz.com/privacy-settings) and clicking on Download a Copy of your Data.

**Delete Your Information**. To request permanent deletion of your personal information, please contact us as described in the Contact Us section or go to your Houzz [settings](https://www.houzz.com/privacy-settings) and click on Delete my Houzz Account as further outlined [here](https://help.houzz.com/s/article/How-do-I-delete-my-account?language=en_US).

**Communications Preferences**. You may change your communication preferences at any time through your Houzz settings if you have a Houzz account and your Ivy settings if you have an Ivy account, and you may also opt-out of similar types of marketing emails from us directly through the email. To opt-out of our text messages at any time, you can follow the instructions provided in the text message, which typically is to reply "STOP." You may opt-out of sales and marketing phone calls from us by letting us know during the call or by contacting us as described in the Contact Us section. Please be aware that you cannot opt-out of receiving necessary account- and privacy-related messages from us. If you wish to stop receiving push notifications from us, you can turn off push notifications for the mobile application in the settings of your mobile device.

**Opt-Out Rights.** Where provided under your local laws, you may opt-out of having your personal information shared with third parties for targeted advertising by visiting "Your Privacy Choices" located in the footer of this website, or by adjusting your account settings here. Additionally, you may use an Opt-out Preference Signal or Universal Opt-out Mechanism to notify us of your privacy preference. We will recognize your opt-out preference, as opting-out of the sale or sharing of your personal information with third parties as defined by applicable law. We will apply your opt-out preference only to the browser or device used to signal your preference. When you login to our Platform, we will apply your opt-out preference to your account.

**Cookie Preferences**. You may opt-out of certain cookies set via the Platform by visiting your Houzz [settings](https://www.houzz.com/settingsAdvanced) or through your browser settings. Please see the "How I can control cookies" section of the [Cookie Policy](https://www.houzz.com/cookiePolicy) for more information.

**Complaints**. If you would like to raise a concern about our use of your information, please contact us first as described in the Contact Us section. We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection or privacy rights in accordance with applicable privacy and data protection laws. Please note, we may also ask you to verify your identity in order to help us respond to your request securely and efficiently. Depending on the laws in your local jurisdiction, you may be able to appeal any decisions made regarding your rights. For individuals in Europe, the United Kingdom, and Switzerland, please see the "International Transfer" section of this Privacy Policy for additional information regarding your rights.

**6\. Data Security and Retention**
-----------------------------------

We use reasonable measures to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction, taking into account the risks involved in the processing and the nature of the personal information.

We will keep your personal information only for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which we are processing your personal information unless the law permits or requires us to retain your personal information for a longer period. For example, we may need to keep your personal information to provide services on our Platform or to defend future legal claims. We also will retain de-identified information after your account has been deleted. Information you have shared with others will remain visible after your account has been deactivated, deleted or after the information has been removed from your own profile or account. Please note that copies of information that you have updated, modified, or deleted may continue to reside in our systems for a period of time, and we may maintain copies of this information as part of our business records.

**7\. Children**
----------------

Our Platform is intended for general audiences and is not directed to children under 18. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 18, we will take reasonable steps to delete that information. If you become aware or believe that a child has provided us with personal information, please contact us as provided in the Contact Us section.

**8\. Updates to this Privacy Policy**
--------------------------------------

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of our Privacy Policy will govern our use of information about you. If we make material changes to our Privacy Policy, we will notify you by email or by posting a notice on our Platform or by other means, to offer you an opportunity to review the changes before they become effective. By continuing to access or use our Platform after those changes become effective, you are subject to the revised Privacy Policy.

**9\. Contact Us**
------------------

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy (including about the manner in which we or our service providers treat your personal information), you may contact us in the following ways:

* If you are an Ivy user, please email us at support@ivy.co;
* if you are a Houzz user and a resident of the European Economic Area, please email us at EUprivacy@houzz.com;
* all other Houzz users, please email us at privacy@houzz.com.

You may also reach our Privacy team by mailing us at our address at Houzz Inc., 8605 Santa Monica Blvd., #90918, West Hollywood, CA 90069-4109, USA, Attn: Privacy.

**10\. International Transfers of Personal Information**
--------------------------------------------------------

We may transfer your personal information to our affiliates, third-party partners, and service providers who are located around the world. When we transfer your information to countries that may not have equivalent privacy and data protection rules to the laws of your country, we take measures to comply with the applicable data protection laws related to our transfer. If you are located in the European Economic Area ("EEA"), the United Kingdom ("UK") or Switzerland, where applicable law requires a transfer mechanism, we ensure that one or more of the following legal frameworks is in place: (a) we comply with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework to receive personal data transfers from the European Union/European Economic Area to the U.S. (see "Data Privacy Framework Notice"), (b) the recipient is based in a jurisdiction that the European Commission has decided maintains an adequate level of protection for personal data, or (c) the recipient has enacted appropriate safeguards under Article 46 of the GDPR (for example Binding Corporate Rules or Standard Contractual Clauses).

### **Data Privacy Framework Notice**

Houzz Inc. and our U.S. affiliates comply with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF), the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF) (collectively, the "DPF") as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce. We have self-certified our commitment to comply with the DPF Principles with respect to personal information we transfer to the United States from the European Economic Area (EEA), the United Kingdom (UK), and Switzerland. If there is ever any conflict between the terms in this Privacy Policy and the DPF Principles, the DPF Principles will govern. Our commitments under the DPF Principles are subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. To learn more about the DPF program, and to view our certification, please visit [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/).

### **Access, Choice, and Onward Transfers**

We describe the types of personal information we receive in the U.S., as well as the purposes for which we collect and use it, in the Collection of Information and Use of Information Sections of this Privacy Policy. If you are located in the EU, UK or Switzerland, you have the right to request access to the personal information that we hold about you and request that we correct, amend or delete your personal information if it is inaccurate or processed in violation of the DPF Principles. We will give you an opportunity to opt out where personal information we collect will be used for a purpose that is materially different from those set out in this Privacy Policy.

We comply with the DPF Principles for all onward transfers of personal information from the EEA, UK, and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions. You can read more about how we share your personal information and the purposes for which we do so, in the Sharing Your Information Section of this Privacy Policy. Under certain circumstances, we may be required to disclose your personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. If you would like to exercise any of your rights, or otherwise wish to limit the use or disclosure of your personal information in accordance with the DPF Principles, please contact us via the contact details set out below.

### **Accountability and Redress**

If you have a question or complaint you believe to be within the scope of our DPF certification, please contact us first at privacy@houzz.com to resolve your concern. We will respond and attempt to resolve your concern within 45 days.

In the event we are unable to resolve your concerns, you can contact our U.S.-based third-party dispute resolution provider (JAMS) at no cost to you, by visiting this [link](https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-data-privacy-framework). Under certain conditions, more fully described in [Annex I](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/article/ANNEX-I-introduction-dpf?tabset-35584=2) on the DPF website, you may be entitled to invoke binding arbitration when certain dispute resolution options do not satisfactorily resolve your concerns.

**11\. Additional Information for Individuals in the United States**
--------------------------------------------------------------------

This section provides notice and specific information to consumers in California, Virginia, Colorado, and Connecticut, including information required by the California Consumer Privacy Act, as amended by the California Privacy Rights Act (collectively "CCPA"), the Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act, the Colorado Consumer Privacy Act, the Connecticut Data Privacy Act, and Utah Consumer Privacy Act. To view additional US state specific information click [here](https://help.houzz.com/s/topic/0TO0y000000kD9cGAE/account-privacy-help?language=en_US).

We share information with third-party partners to display personalized ads and content on other platforms, for which you have the right to opt-out. You may opt-out of sharing your personal information for these purposes by visiting "Your Privacy Choices" located in the footer of this website, or by adjusting your account settings [here](https://www.houzz.com/privacy-settings). Additionally, you may use an Opt-out Preference Signal or Universal Opt-out Mechanism to notify us of your privacy preference. We will recognize your opt-out preference, as opting-out of the sale or sharing of your personal information with third parties as defined by applicable law. We will apply your opt-out preference only to the browser or device used to signal your preference. When you login to our Platform, we will apply your opt-out preference to your account.

As provided in our Terms of Use, use of the Houzz Platform by anyone under 18 years of age is strictly prohibited. Consequently, we do not knowingly disclose information regarding individuals under 18 years of age to third parties in exchange for consideration. We do not use or disclose sensitive personal information for purposes other than those set forth in the CCPA. In addition to the rights described above and in the Your Choices and Rights section, California residents may also, subject to certain exceptions, request us to provide information about how we have used and shared your personal information in the previous 12 months. Residents of California, Virginia, Colorado, and Connecticut also have the right to request correction of inaccurate personal information. Residents of Virginia, Colorado, Connecticut, and Utah have the right to confirm whether Houzz is processing their personal information. Please submit these requests for information, as well as requests to access, correct, or delete your information, through this [online support form](https://help.houzz.com/s/contactsupport?language=en_US), through your [privacy settings](https://www.houzz.com/privacy-settings), or by emailing us at privacy@houzz.com. Residents of California, Virginia, Colorado, and Connecticut may appeal Houzz's decision regarding their request by contacting us at privacy@houzz.com. If we deny your request, we will notify you and provide our reasons for the denial and instructions regarding the rights you may have under applicable laws to appeal the decision. If the appeal is denied, we will notify you of your rights under applicable laws to contact the Attorney General to submit a complaint. Consistent with applicable privacy laws, except to the extent reasonably related to the value of your personal information, we will not treat you differently for exercising your rights under these laws.

Your authorized agent may exercise your data protection rights on your behalf [via this online support form](https://help.houzz.com/s/contactsupport?language=en_US) or by emailing us at privacy@houzz.com. We may still require you to directly verify your identity and confirm that you have provided the authorized agent permission to submit the request. Please keep in mind that if we do not receive adequate proof that you are authorized to act on the consumer's behalf, we may deny the request. Whether you submit your request directly or through an authorized agent, generally, the only means Houzz has to verify your identity is for you to respond to a specific Houzz email from the Houzz support team from the email address associated with your Houzz account or to click a confirmation or similar button in a specific Houzz email from the email address associated with your Houzz account.

We collect, use, and disclose personal information for the following purposes:

* to provide and improve our Platform and its features and functionality;
* to evaluate use of our Platform for our business purposes and to provide and improve our products and services;
* to personalize your experience;
* to display relevant or targeted advertising (on our Platform and third-party sites) for us and other businesses and to evaluate the success of such advertising;
* to provide feedback to professionals and merchants on our Platform;
* to communicate with you as described in our agreements with you (for example, the Houzz [Terms of Use](https://www.houzz.com/termsOfUse)) or this Privacy Policy;
* to prevent fraud and to maintain a quality experience for our business purposes or legal reasons (for example, the Houzz [Terms of Use](https://www.houzz.com/termsOfUse));
* to enforce compliance with our agreements with you (for example, the Houzz [Terms of Use](https://www.houzz.com/termsOfUse)) and applicable law; to comply with our legal obligations; to prosecute or defend a lawsuit, arbitration, or similar legal proceeding; to respond to lawful requests by public authorities (including national security or law enforcement requirements);
* to perform research and analysis for our business purposes and to conduct journalist research;
* to award badges and similar designations and if you decide to participate, to administer surveys, contests, and promotions;
* to inform your contacts who have accounts on our Platform that you also have joined our Platform and follow them on your behalf so that you may view their public activities on our Platform;
* to provide quality assurance purposes and training;
* to understand and help manage the quality of requests received, and responses sent, by professionals and sellers on our Platform and to provide them with feedback;
* to review your communications and improve user experience, including using automated technology. [Learn more](https://help.houzz.com/s/article/Automated-Communications-Technology?language=en_US).
* to identify you and log your use across devices, our Platform, and third-party sites;
* to store information about the payment method you use in connection with the Platform;
* to make information available to you about any prior purchases completed using the email address for your account if you make purchases on Houzz as a visitor and subsequently create an account; and
* to show you all of your payments, as well as invoices, proposals, retainers, and similar documents on a per-project basis if you are a client on Ivy.

Learn more below about the types of personal information that we collect, disclose for a business purpose, share for targeted advertising, disclose for valuable services, and disclose for money, about the intended data retention period for such data, and about the third parties to which we disclose such data. When you close your account, we take steps to delete your data. The Collection of Information section of this Privacy Policy describes the sources from which we collect your personal information. The Sharing Your Information section of this Privacy Policy describes the types of third parties with which we share your personal information.

| Categories of Personal Information we Collect | Disclose for a business purpose | Sharing for behavioral targeted advertising | Disclose for valuable services | Third Parties to which we Disclose Personal Data | Disclose for money | Intended Data Retention Period |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Identifiers (for example, real name, address, email address, account name, user ID, device identifiers, IP address, or other similar identifiers) | Yes | Yes | Yes (e.g. advertising) | Professionals, vendors and sellers on our Platform, advertising providers, and other service providers | No  | As long as the account is active or as legally required or permitted |
| Customer Records (for example, customer records containing personal information, such as name, signature, address, telephone number, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information) | Yes | No  | No  | Professionals, vendors and sellers on our Platform, and other service providers, except for payment information which will be only shared with payment processors | No  | As long as the account is active or as legally required or permitted |
| Protected Classifications (for example, gender, age, and ethnicity) | No (except gender and ethnicity may be published at your direction) | No  | No  | N/A | No  | As long as the account is active or as legally required or permitted |
| Commercial Information (for example, records of products, services purchased or considered, and purchase preferences) | Yes | Yes | Yes (e.g. advertising) | Professionals, vendors and sellers on our Platform, advertising providers, and other service providers | No  | As long as the account is active or as legally required or permitted |
| Internet Activity Information (for example, browsing history, search history, and interactions with an Internet website, application or advertisement) | Yes | Yes | Yes (e.g. advertising) | Professionals, vendors and sellers on our Platform, advertising providers, and other service providers | No  | As long as the account is active or as legally required or permitted |
| Audiovisual (for example, audio, photos, videos, or similar information) | Yes (only if you choose to provide this information) | No  | No  | N/A | No  | As long as the account is active or as legally required or permitted |
| Precise Geolocation Data (for example, latitude/longitude from a particular device) | No  | No  | No  | N/A | No  | As long as the account is active or as legally required or permitted |
| Work History (for example, professional or employment-related information) | Yes (if this information is provided) | No  | No  | N/A | No  | As long as the account is active or as legally required or permitted |
| Inferences (for example, inferences drawn from any of the information identified above to create a profile about a consumer reflecting preferences and behavior) | Yes | No  | No  | N/A | No  | As long as the account is active or as legally required or permitted |

Effective February 15, 2024

    United States
    
    Select countryUnited StatesUnited KingdomAustraliaDeutschlandFranceРоссия日本ItaliaEspañaDanmarkSverigeIrelandSingaporeNew ZealandIndia
    
    © 2024 Houzz Inc.
    
* * ### COMPANY
        
    * [Privacy](https://www.houzz.com/privacyPolicy) & [Notice](https://www.houzz.com/privacyPolicy#12)
* * ### BUSINESS SERVICES
        
* * ### GET HELP
        
* * ### CONNECT WITH US

United Kingdom

Australia - EnglishCanada - EnglishDanmark - DanskDeutschland - DeutschEspaña - EspañolFrance - FrançaisIndia - EnglishIreland - EnglishItalia - Italiano日本 - 日本語New Zealand - EnglishРоссия - РусскийSingapore - EnglishSverige - SvenskaUnited Kingdom - EnglishUS - English

Tailor my experience with cookies

Houzz uses cookies and similar technologies to personalise my experience, serve me relevant content, and improve Houzz products and services. By clicking ‘Accept’ I agree to this, as further described in the [Houzz Cookie Policy](https://www.houzz.com/cookiePolicy). I can reject non-essential cookies by clicking ‘Manage Preferences’.

Manage PreferencesAccept
